RG 002:004, General Assembly Papers
Connecticut State Library
- 1913-1971, 1984-045
  - 1923
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 600-908; Labor; Military Affairs; New Towns and Probate Districts; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; State Parks (Box 79)
  - 1925
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 80)
    - Public Acts, 1-146 (Box 81)
    - Public Acts, 147-269 (Box 82)
    - Special Acts, 1-184 (Box 83)
    - Special Acts, 185-320 (Box 84)
    - Special Acts, 321-477 (Box 85)
    - Special Acts, 478-503 (Box 86)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims (Box 87)
    - Rejected Bills - Contested Elections; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Finance; Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 88)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 6-467 (Box 89)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 469-1053; Labor; Manufacturers; Military Affairs; Public Health and Safety; Roads, Rivers and Bridges (Box 90)
    - Rejected Bills - Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Miscellaneous, Change of Reference, No action taken, Tabled (Box 91)
  - 1927
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Appointments (Box 92)
    - Public Acts, 1-174 (Box 93)
    - Public Acts, 175-283 (Box 94)
    - Public Acts, 284-327 (Box 95)
    - Special Acts, 1-139 (Box 96)
    - Special Acts, 140-284 (Box 97)
    - Special Acts, 285-389 (Box 98)
    - Special Acts, 390-492 (Box 99)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Capital Furniture; Cities and Boroughs; Claims (Box 100)
    - Rejected Bills - Constitutional Amendments; Education; Finance; Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 101)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 1-485 (Box 102)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 489-771; Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety (Box 103)
    - Rejected Bills - Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; Sales of Lands; State Parks and Reservations (Box 104)
  - 1929
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Appointments; Constitutional Amendments; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 105)
    - Public Acts, 1-199 (Box 106)
    - Public Acts, 200-303 (Box 107)
    - Special Acts, 1-153 (Box 108)
    - Special Acts, 154-291 (Box 109)
    - Special Acts, 292-433 (Box 110)
    - Special Acts, 434-513 (Box 111)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments (Box 112)
    - Rejected Bills - Education; Finance; Fish and Game; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 4-255 (Box 113)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 226-848; Labor; Military Affairs; Motor vehicles (Box 114)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Health and Safety; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; State Prisons (Box 115)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Appointments; Constitutional Amendments; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 116)
  - 1931
    - Public Acts, 1-183 (Box 117)
    - Public Acts, 184-293 (Box 118)
    - Special Acts, 1-174 (Box 119)
    - Special Acts, 175-325 (Box 120)
    - Special Acts, 326-434 (Box 121)
    - Special Acts, 435-570 (Box 122)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Federal Relations (Box 123)
    - Rejected Bills - Finance; Fish and Game; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Impeachments (Box 124)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 6-449 (Box 125)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 451-947; Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles (Box 126)
    - Rejected Bills - New Counties and Seats; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges (Box 127)
  - 1933
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Constitutional Amendments; Appointments (Box 128)
    - Public Acts, 1-215 (Box 129)
    - Public Acts, 216-331 (Box 130)
    - Special Acts, 1-219 (Box 131)
    - Special Acts, 220-358 (Box 132)
    - Special Acts, 359-526 (Box 133)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Capital Furniture; Cities and Boroughs (Box 134)
    - Rejected Bills - Claims; Congressional and Senatorial Districts; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Federal Relations; Finance; Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 135)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 4-586 (Box 136)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 587-1136; Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles (Box 137)
    - Rejected Bills - New Towns and Probate Districts; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; State Parks and Reservations; State Prisons; Miscellaneous (Box 138)
  - 1935
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Orders on the Treasury; Appointments; Resolutions; House; Senate; Joint House; Joint Senate (Box 139)
    - Public Acts, 1-154 (Box 140)
    - Public Acts, 155-256 (Box 141)
    - Public Acts, 257-328 (Box 142)
    - Special Acts, 1-200 (Box 143)
    - Special Acts, 201-376 (Box 144)
    - Special Acts, 377-518 (Box 145)
      Does not include Special Acts, 410-413.
    - Special Acts, 519-537 (Box 146)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appointments; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs (Box 147)
    - Rejected Bills - Cities and Boroughs; Education; Finance; Federal Relations; Fish and Game (Box 148)
    - Rejected Bills - Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 5-543 (Box 149)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 544-1190 (Box 150)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; State Parks; State Prisons (Box 151)
    - Rejected Bills - Miscellaneous, Unfinished, Tabled, No action taken (Box 152)
  - Special Session, 1936 (Box 153)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Public Acts; Special Acts; Rejected Bills; Business from previous Sessions to 1889 (Box 153)
  - 1937
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Canvasses of Votes; Appointments; Reports (Box 154)
    - Public Acts, 1-163 (Box 155)
    - Public Acts, 164-281 (Box 156)
    - Public Acts, 282-454 (Box 157)
    - Special Acts, 1-177 (Box 158)
    - Special Acts, 178-354 (Box 159)
    - Special Acts, 355-500 (Box 160)
    - Special Acts, 501-615 (Box 161)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs (Box 162)
    - Rejected Bills; Cities and Boroughs; Education; Federal Relations; Finance (Box 163)
    - Rejected Bills - Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights; Highway Safety; Incorporations; Insurance; interstate cooperation; Judiciary, Senate Bills, 7-350 (Box 164)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 351-1088; Judiciary, House Bills, 204-578 (Box 165)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 579-1393, 1695; Labor; Military Affairs (Box 166)
    - Rejected Bills - Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety (Box 167)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Welfare; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; State Parks and Reservations; State Prisons (Box 168)
    - Bills on which no further action was taken and Unfinished Business (Box 169)
  - 1939
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions; Appointments; Contested Elections; Reports (Box 170)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Public Acts, 1-151 (Box 171)
    - Public Acts, 152-300 (Box 172)
    - Public Acts, 301-368 (Box 173)
    - Special Acts, 1-163 (Box 174)
    - Special Acts, 164-317 (Box 175)
    - Special Acts, 318-475 (Box 176)
    - Special Acts, 476-595 (Box 177)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Constitutional Amendments; Cities and Boroughs (Box 178)
    - Rejected Bills - Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Education; Federal Relations; Finance (Box 179)
    - Rejected Bills - Fish and game; Forfeited Rights; Human Institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, Senate Bills, 7-602 (Box 180)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 625-921; Judiciary, House Bills, 15-682 (Box 181)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 687-1723 (Box 182)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety (Box 183)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Welfare; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Reorganization; State Library; State Parks; State Prisons; Shell Fisheries (Box 184)
  - 1941
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Canvasses of Votes; Senate and House Resolutions (Box 185)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments (Box 186)
    - Public Acts, 1-165 (Box 187)
    - Public Acts, 166-293 (Box 188)
    - Public Acts, 295-360 (Box 189)
    - Special Acts, 1-178 (Box 190)
    - Special Acts, 179-347 (Box 191)
    - Special Acts, 348-463 (Box 192)
    - Special Acts, 464-564 (Box 193)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Capital Furniture; Cities and Boroughs (Box 194)
    - Rejected Bills - Cities and Boroughs; Education (Box 195)
    - Rejected Bills - Education; Finance; Fish and Game; Forfeited Rights (Box 196)
    - Rejected Bills - Humane institutions; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, Senate Bills, 19-1063 (Box 197)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 1064-1174 (Box 198)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 19-1074 (Box 199)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 1075-1838 (Box 200)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety (Box 201)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Utilities; Public Welfare; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; State Administration; Insurance; State Parks and Reservations; Unfinished Business; Bills on which no further action was taken (Box 202)
  - 1943
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Amendments; Resolutions (Box 203)
    - Public Acts, 1-155 (Box 204)
    - Public Acts, 156-294 (Box 205)
    - Public Acts, 295-422 (Box 206)
    - Special Acts, 1-171 (Box 207)
    - Special Acts, 172-326 (Box 208)
    - Special Acts, 327-475 (Box 209)
    - Special Acts, 476-560 (Box 210)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs (Box 211)
    - Rejected Bills - Constitutional Amendments; Claims; Education; Federal Relations; Finance (Box 212)
    - Rejected Bills - Finance; Fish and Game; Insurance; Judiciary, Senate Bills, 5-724 (Box 213)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 726-785; Judiciary, House Bills, 25-1077 (Box 214)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety; Public Welfare; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges (Box 215)
    - Rejected Bills - Unfinished Business (Box 216)
  - Special Session, 1944 January, June (Box 217)
  - 1945
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Amendments; Executive Nominations; Orders on the Treasury; Orders of War; Resolutions (Box 218)
    - Public Acts, 1-180 (Box 219)
    - Public Acts, 191-330 (Box 220)
    - Public Acts, 331-464 (Box 221)
    - Special Acts, 1-168 (Box 222)
    - Special Acts, 170-345 (Box 223)
    - Special Acts, 346-444 (Box 224)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Constitutional Amendments; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Education; Elections; Federal Relations (Box 225)
    - Rejected Bills - Finance; Fish and Game; Incorporations; Insurance; Judiciary, 16-492 (Box 226)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, 493-737; Labor; Licensed Occupations; Liquor Control; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles (Box 227)
    - Rejected Bills - Penal Institutions; Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel; Public Utilities; Public Welfare; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; State Parks (Box 228)
    - Unfinished Business (Box 229)
    - Unfinished Business, no action taken (Box 230)
  - Special Session, 1946 May (Box 217)
  - 1947
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Canvasses Reports; Resolutions; Orders on the Treasury; Constitutional Amendments; Reports to the General Assembly (Box 231)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Executive Nominations; Superior Court; Court of Common Pleas; Town Court; City Court; Borough Court; Senate Appointments; General Assembly Appointments; County Commissioners (Box 232)
    - Constitutional Amendments; Forfeited Rights; Term of Judges of Probate; Election of State Officers for Four Year Term; Professional Appointments of Judges of Minor Courts (Box 233)
    - Forfeited rights (Box 234)
    - Public Acts, 1-141 (Box 235)
    - Public Acts, 142-234 (Box 236)
    - Public Acts, 235-349 (Box 237)
    - Public Acts, 350-462 (Box 238)
    - Public Acts, 463-538 (Box 239)
    - Special Acts, 1-134 (Box 240)
    - Special Acts, 135-201 (Box 241)
    - Special Acts, 202-311 (Box 242)
    - Special Acts, 312-351 (Box 243)
    - Special Acts, 352-510 (Box 244)
    - Special Acts, 511-538 (Box 245)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Engrossed Bills; Elections (Box 246)
    - Rejected Bills - Federal Relations; Finance; Fish and Game; Incorporations; Insurance; Federal and Inter-Government Relations (Box 247)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 2-371; Judiciary, House Bills, 16-546 (Box 248)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 670-1399; Labor; Licensed Occupations; Liquor Control; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Penal Institutions; Public Buildings and Grounds; Preliminary and Unimportant; Rejected House Resolutions (Box 249)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Health and Safety; Public personnel; Public utilities; Public Welfare; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Shell Fisheries; State Parks and Reservations; Veterans Affairs; Unfinished Business, A-F (Box 250)
    - Rejected Bills - Unfinished Business, F-Z (Box 251)
  - Special Session, 1948 February, August (Box 252)
  - 1949
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 253)
    - Public Acts, 1-159 (Box 254)
    - Public Acts, 169-279 (Box 255)
    - Public Acts, 280-358 (Box 256)
    - Special Acts, 1-185 (Box 257)
    - Special Acts, 186-327 (Box 258)
    - Special Acts, 328-475 (Box 259)
    - Special Acts, 476-547 (Box 260)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; contested Elections; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Elections (Box 261)
    - Rejected Bills - Federal and Inter-Government Relations; Finance; Fish and Game; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 262)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 36-1348 (Box 263)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House Bills, 1351-1669; Judiciary, Senate Bills, 35-1021 (Box 264)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor; Liquor Control; Military and Veterans Affairs; Motor Vehicles; Penal Institutions; Public Buildings and Grounds; Public Health and Safety; Public Information; Public Personnel, Senate (Box 265)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Personnel, House; Public utilities; Public Welfare and Human Institutions; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Rules; State Parks and Reservations (Box 266)
    - Unfinished Business - A-I (Box 267)
    - Unfinished Business - J-R (Box 268)
    - Action taken, Agriculture to Judiciary, Senate (Box 269)
    - Action taken, Judiciary, House to State Parks and Reservations (Box 270)
  - Special Session, 1949 June 14, October 5, November 9 (Box 271)
    - Resolutions; Public Acts; Special Acts; Appointments; Unfinished Business; no action taken; Rump Session, July 6; Governor's message; Resolutions-Bills (Box 271)
  - Special Session, 1950 March 9, September (Box 272)
    - Resolutions; Public Acts; Special Acts; Appointment; Rejected Bills and Resolutions (Box 272)
  - 1951
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 273)
    - Public Acts, 1-100 (Box 274)
    - Public Acts, 101-190 (Box 275)
    - Public Acts, 191-290 (Box 276)
    - Public Acts, 291-386 (Box 277)
    - Special Acts, 1-120 (Box 278)
    - Special Acts, 121-240 (Box 279)
    - Special Acts, 241-370 (Box 280)
    - Special Acts, 371-490 (Box 281)
    - Special Acts, 491-569 (Box 282)
    - Special Acts, 570-618 (Box 283)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Aviation; Banks; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Education; Elections; Engrossed Bills; Federal and Inter-Government Relations; Finance; Fish and Game; Incorporations; Insurance (Box 284)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House and Senate; Labor; Liquor Control; Military and Veterans Affairs; Civil Defense (Box 285)
    - Rejected Bills - Motor Vehicles; Penal Institution; Public Buildings and Grounds; Public Health and Safety; Public Personnel; Public Utilities (Box 286)
    - Rejected Bills - Public Welfare and Human Institutions; Railroads; Roads, Rivers and Bridges (Box 287)
    - Unfinished Business - A-C; Cities and Boroughs, Senate (Box 288)
    - Unfinished Business - Cities and Boroughs, House (Box 289)
    - Unfinished Business - Claims and Insurance (Box 290)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate and House (Box 291)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House; Labor (Box 292)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control to Rules (Box 293)
    - Special Session, June 13 (Box 294)
  - 1953
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Appointments; Amendments; Resolutions (Box 295)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate Resolutions; Courts (Box 296)
    - Public Acts, 1-135 (Box 297)
    - Public Acts, 136-260 (Box 298)
    - Public Acts, 261-367 (Box 299)
    - Public Acts, 368-435 (Box 300)
    - Public Acts, 436-516 (Box 301)
    - Special Acts, 1-130 (Box 302)
    - Special Acts, 131-260 (Box 303)
    - Special Acts, 261-365 (Box 304)
    - Special Acts, 366-500 (Box 305)
    - Special Acts, 501-610 (Box 306)
    - Special Acts, 611-629 (Box 307)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Appropriations; Cities and Boroughs; Claims; Constitutional Amendments; Education (Box 308)
    - Rejected Bills - Elections; Federal and Inter-Government Relations; Finance (Box 309)
    - Rejected Bills - Fish and Game; Incorporations; Judiciary, House and Senate (Box 310)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, House; Labor; Liquor Control; Military Affairs; Motor Vehicles (Box 311)
    - Rejected Bills - Penal Institutions; Public Health and Safety; Public Buildings and Grounds; Public Personnel; Public Welfare and Human Institutions; Public Utilities; Resolutions not assigned to Committee; Roads, Rivers and Bridges; Rules; State Parks and Reservations (Box 312)
    - Unfinished Business - A-E (Box 313)
    - Unfinished Business - F-Judiciary, Senate Bills, 7-69 (Box 314)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House Bills, 922-1758 to Military and Veterans Affairs (Box 315)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate Bill, 692; Judiciary, House Bills, 71-203 (Box 316)
    - Unfinished Business - Motor Vehicles; Public Health and Safety (Box 317)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel to State Parks and Reservations (Box 318)
  - 1955
    - Preliminary and Unimportant (Box 319)
    - Appointments (Box 320)
    - Public Acts, 1-160 (Box 321)
    - Public Acts, 161-300 (Box 322)
    - Public Acts, 301-400 (Box 323)
    - Public Acts, 401-515 (Box 324)
    - Public Acts, 516-563 (Box 325)
    - Special Acts, 1-190 (Box 326)
    - Special Acts, 191-350 (Box 327)
    - Special Acts, 351-490 (Box 328)
    - Special Acts, 491-598 (Box 329)
    - Special Acts, 599-672 (Box 330)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture; Federal and Inter-Government Relations (Box 331)
    - Rejected Bills - Finance to Judiciary, Senate Bills, 3-838 (Box 332)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 844-1269; Judiciary, House Bills; Labor; Liquor Control (Box 333)
    - Rejected Bills - Motor Vehicles to State Parks and Reservations (Box 334)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture to Cities and Boroughs; House Bill 795 (Box 335)
    - Unfinished Business - Cities and Boroughs; House Bill 801 to Federal and Inter-Government Relations (Box 336)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance (Box 337)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance; House Bill 916 to Judiciary, Senate Bill 122 (Box 338)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, Senate Bills, 123-1194 (Box 339)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary, House Bills, 5-2149 (Box 340)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor (Box 341)
    - Unfinished Business - Liquor Control; Public personnel (Box 342)
    - Bills ruled out of order and changes of reference (Box 343)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Personnel to State Parks and Reservations (Box 344)
    - Special Session - Preliminary and Unimportant, June (Box 345)
    - Special Session - Public and Special Acts, June (Box 346)
    - Special Session - Preliminary and Unimportant, November (Box 347)
    - Special Session - Public Acts, November (Box 348)
    - Special Session - Special Acts, November (Box 349)
  - 1957
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Resolutions (Box 350)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant; Appointments; Constitutional Amendments referred to Session (Box 351)
    - Public Acts, 1-124 (Box 352)
    - Public Acts, 125-250 (Box 353)
    - Public Acts, 251-363 (Box 354)
    - Public Acts, 364-459 (Box 355)
    - Public Acts, 450-557 (Box 356)
    - Public Acts, 558-619 (Box 357)
    - Public Acts, 620-673 (Box 358)
    - Special Acts, 1-132 (Box 359)
    - Special Acts, 133-162 (Box 360)
    - Special Acts, 217-307 (Box 361)
    - Special Acts, 308-468 (Box 362)
    - Special Acts, 469-561 (Box 363)
    - Special Acts, 562-679 (Box 364)
    - Rejected Bills - Banks; Fish and Game (Box 365)
    - Rejected Bills - General Law to Judiciary and Government Functions (Box 366)
    - Rejected Bills - Labor to Water Resolutions and Flood Control (Box 367)
    - Unfinished Business - Agriculture to Claims (Box 368)
    - Unfinished Business - Constitutional Amendments to Finance (Box 369)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance to General Law (Box 370)
    - Unfinished Business - General Law to Labor (Box 371)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor and Judiciary to Government Functions (Box 372)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Government Functions (Box 373)
    - Unfinished Business - Judiciary and Government Functions (Box 374)
    - Unfinished Business - Incorporations; Judiciary; Public Personnel (Box 375)
    - Unfinished Business - Public Utilities to Water Resolutions, and no Committees (Box 376)
    - Special Session - Preliminary and Unimportant; Unfinished Business; out of order, September (Box 377)
  - Special Session, 1958 March (Box 378)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant; Rejected Bills; Unfinished Business; out of order (Box 378)
    - Public Acts; Special Acts (Box 379)
  - 1959
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - Senate Resolutions; Senate Joint Resolutions (Box 380)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House Resolutions; House Joint Resolutions (Box 381)
    - Preliminary and Unimportant - House and Senate Resolutions (Box 382)
    - Initiation of Local Legislation (Box 382A)
    - Public Acts, 1-111 (Box 383)
    - Public Acts, 112-151 (Box 384)
    - Public Acts, 152-275 (Box 385)
    - Public Acts, 276-404 (Box 386)
    - Public Acts, 405-520 (Box 387)
    - Public Acts, 521-600 (Box 388)
    - Public Acts, 601-650 (Box 389)
    - Public Acts, 651-688 (Box 390)
    - Special Acts, 1-166 (Box 391)
    - Special Acts, 167-333 (Box 392)
    - Special Acts, 334-465 (Box 393)
    - Special Acts, 466-580 (Box 394)
    - Rejected Bills - Agriculture to Insurance (Box 395)
    - Rejected Bills - Judiciary and Government Relations to Water Resolutions (Box 396)
    - Unfinished Business - Preliminary and Unimportant; Agriculture to Cities and Boroughs (Box 397)
    - Unfinished Business - Cities and Boroughs to Constitutional Amendments (Box 398)
    - Unfinished Business - Education to Finance (Box 399)
    - Unfinished Business - Finance to General Law (Box 400)
    - Unfinished Business - Incorporations to Judiciary and Government Functions (Box 401)
    - Unfinished Business - Labor to Penal Institutions (Box 402)